

Contact

- Haarlem, The Netherlands
- davidmendiluce@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/davidMarcosM/
- github.com/DavidMendiluce

Personal Skills

Agile Methodology

Cambridge English
Certificate Level C1

B2 Driving License

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science (BCompSc), Computer science

Universidad Complutense de Madrid

David Marcos — Front End Developer

Profile

I am a Front-End developer with great skills in React and Vue frameworks and I am used to a test driven and CI environment using Cypress and Jenkins. I have successfully worked as a freelancer in different teams and interesting projects such as Progressive Web Applications and Management Systems. Code quality is really important to me, and I strive to deliver code that follows the 'SOLID' and 'DRY' principles.

Work Experience

· Front-End Developer at Hoteliga

(January 2022 - November 2022)

Tech Stack: AngularJS, NET, Azure, Virtual Machines, CI pipelines

- o Adding features with AngularJS such as custom forms or subscriptions
- o Task management through Jira
- Working on blogs section of the website
- Implementing features and APIs such as reCaptcha or goggle tag manager
- Maintenance of the website
- Website optimization for example with image handling through s3
- · Full-Stack developer at Qinta

(October 2019 - September 2021)

Tech Stack: AngularJS, PHP, HTML/CSS, MySQL, PWA, Javascript

- Implementing Figma mockup designs into working website features together with a UI designer
- o Database design and creation in MySQL
- Handeling state changes, requests to PHP and data formating with AngularJS as Front-End Framework
- Setting deadlines and following those deadlines to comply with the different requirements and phases of the prototype
- Implementing Progressive Web Application functionality and handling cache data to run some parts of the application offline
- Front-End Developer at Clarewell Clinics

(November 2018 - August 2019)

Tech Stack: WordPress, PHP Hooks, JQuery, Plugin Development

- WordPress website maintenance
- Adding and creating custom WordPress plugins to add new features such as search engines
- Fixing issues from Themes and Plugins
- Customizing themes

Recent Projects

Vuex Application

Tech Stack: Vue, Vuex, Responsive CSS, Javascript, AXIOS, Cypress

Vue single page application which consist of a real state website that uses Vuex for state management and AXIOS for API requests. Its fully responsive, offers CRUD operation and other features such as sorting, reactive search and image uploading.

Link: https://vuehouses.space

Redux Application

Tech Stack: React, Redux, Responsive CSS, Javascript, Cypress

React application based on a real state website that features animations and connection to the maps API. The application uses Redux for the state management and react custom libraries.

Link: https://atix.website